Stephanie A. Mizelle

C: 317-797-0712

Email: samizelle@gmail.com

Portfolio: https://samizelle.github.io/

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/stephanie-mizelle-1763b2168/

Summary

I am a former administrative professional with a 20-year background in payroll administration, employee benefits administration, human resources, and employee management. I am currently a student at Eleven Fifty Academy in the .NET Cohort. Upon graduation in January 2019, I will have accrued 500+ hours of handson experience with .NET coding, HTML and CSS. I will be seeking an opportunity to continue to enhance my new skills and be a valuable participant in a professional environment. I am highly detail-oriented and organized, love working with numbers and systems to extract and analyze data.

Highlights

- .Net framework
- SOL
- HTML/CSS
- Angular

- Report generation and analysis
- Problem solving
- Costs analysis
- MS Excel, MS Word

Education

Eleven Fifty Academy .NET Cohort

Fishers, IN January, 2019

Ball State University BS, Office Systems Administration

Muncie, IN January, 1987

Experience

Sapphire Holdings, Inc., dba The Cleaning Authority – Indianapolis South Plainfield, IN September 2016 – November 2017

Owned and operated franchise of residential cleaning service. Responsible for all aspects of business, including staffing, scheduling, sales, payroll, invoice processing, bank deposits and reconciliations, procurement, customer relations, employee management, and day-to-day operations.

Avon Community School Corporation

Avon, IN

December 2015 - September 2016

Guidance Secretary - Avon High School

Provided administrative support to administrators, staff, students, and parents in fast-paced environment in High School Guidance Office. Utilized PowerSchool to track attendance, provide information and reports to staff and students.

Wabash Valley Power Association

Indianapolis, IN

March 1987 - January 2005

Compensation/Benefits Administrator - 2003-2005 Manager, Human Resources - 1996-2003 Payroll/Benefits Coordinator - 1988-1996 Department Secretary - Administrative Division - 1987-1988 Over 18-year career with company, responsibilities included:

All facets of benefits administration for all employee benefit plans. Served as liaison between employees and vendors. Handled all benefit billings and reconciliations of general ledger accounts.

All aspects of company's semi-monthly and bi-weekly payroll, from manual calculation to implementation of payroll module of integrated accounting system and later conversion to ADP software platform.

Used MS Excel to create complex spreadsheets and automate reporting for Payroll Register, salary history, and time tracking. Developed spreadsheets and reports to track all changes to payroll cycles to verify accuracy.

Managed corporate HR function and supervised two employees in department. Responsible for all aspects of HR, including compensation, recruiting and staffing, policy development, and strategic planning.